jog.fm 2015-03-16

# Privacy Policy | Workout songs and playlists - jog.fm

_Last Updated: August 16, 2011_

## A message from the jog.fm team

We're people just like you. We care about our privacy, we hate pop-up and pop-under ads, **we despise spam** , we dislike obligatory registrations, and we really don't like insecure websites. We spent a lot of time making sure our site was secure, and as private as you'd like it to be. We have, and will continue to reject distasteful, or otherwise "sketchy" ads. We'll never spam, or distribute your email address to anyone. **And more importantly, we've built the site so you can use most of the functionality without an account.**

If you have any questions or concerns about the privacy of this site, please [contact us](mailto:hello@jog.fm). We're willing to go well out of our way to make sure you have a safe, enjoyable experience on our site.

## Quick Overview of this Policy

1\. You must be at least 13 years old to use this site. If you are under 17, you should ask permission from your parent or guardian.

2\. For instances where you need an account (e.g. playlist creation), your email address is the only personally identifiable information we require.

3\. **We will NOT release, display, sell, or otherwise distribute your email address.** We will not display information regarding your third-party authentications (e.g. Twitter, Facebook usernames). However, if you use your email address as your username or in the title of your playlist, it may be visible on the website. **Please do not use your email address or your real name as your username.**

4\. We do not allow visitors to view your profile unless they are logged in to our site. In that case, they can see any information you provided on your profile (e.g. answers to profile questions, etc). Your username may be visible to visitors who are not logged in to the site.

5\. We use [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/analytics/) for analytics. They have standard privacy policies, but you should review them as well.

6\. We use cookies to keep you logged in and to provide a more personalized experience. 

7\. We might serve advertisements from third parties. We have and will continue to reject advertisers who interfere with this Policy.

8\. We keep your data secure. Especially your password.

## Privacy Policy

Blendist LLC ("Blendist", "we", "our", or "us") owns or controls, and provides users ("Users") access to the web pages located at jog.fm, and the associated subdomains including but not limited to walk.jog.fm, cycle.jog.fm, and ride.jog.fm (the "Website"), and all proprietary services, software, mobile applications, data and materials accessed via the Website (the "Services"). The Website and the Services are referred to together in this Privacy Policy as the "Properties". 

Your privacy and security are some of our top concerns. Accordingly, we have developed this Privacy Policy (the "Policy") in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines the Policy. 

##  1\. Audience 

**Children under the age of 13 are not eligible to use our Properties** and must not attempt to register with the Properties and/or submit any personal information. We do not knowingly collect personal information from any person who is under the age of 13 or allow them to register. If it comes to our attention that we have collected personal data from a person under the age of 13, we will remove this information as quickly as possible. If you have reason to believe that this has occurred, please contact us at [legal@jog.fm](mailto:legal@jog.fm), and we will delete all relevant information. 

Persons between the ages of 13 and 17 should not send any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet without asking for parental/legal guardian permission beforehand. 

##  2\. Revisions to the Policy 

While we will attempt to notify you of updates, this Policy may be amended without notice to you. It is your responsibility to read the Policy carefully and review any changes that may have been made. 

##  3\. Personal Information 

For purposes of this Policy, the terms "personal information" and "personally identifiable information" shall mean all information provided during your initial registration on the Properties and during your creation of a user profile, including, but not limited to, your real name, email address, postal address and other location information, your age, your gender and certain other demographic information or information that may enable online or offline contact with you. 

**While we make a concerted effort to provide access to as many features of the Properties as possible without requiring personal information, some features (such as playlist creation) require user registration.** When registering you will be asked to provide an email address and create a username and password. You may also choose to create a more detailed profile of yourself on the Properties by submitting additional personal information. Your username and additional personal information will be publicly visible to Users of the Properties. We will never publish or display your email address, unless it is used as your username. **Please note that if you choose a username that includes or reveals your real name, email address, or any other personal information, such information may be available to other Users of the Properties and to the general public.**

If you choose to purchase music or other goods or services by clicking on a third party link provided on the Website (e.g. a link to iTunes or Amazon.com), such third party may collect your personal details for the purpose of completing a transaction (e.g. credit card number). We may be provided with confirmation of your transactions with such third parties and, in some instances, such confirmation may include your personal information. Aside from such confirmations, the only information that we will collect with respect to such third party links is: (a) the number of Users who utilized such links; and (b) the number of purchases made by these Users. 

Where you upload photographs or other content as part of your user profile, you should be aware that Blendist is entitled to use those photographs and content in accordance with our [Terms of Use](http://jog.fm/pages/terms "Terms of Use"). Blendist discourages users from uploading photographs of, or created by other people without their permission. 

##  4\. Statistical, Browser, and Location-based Information 

As a service, we may collect certain aggregate statistical information in order to understand the likes and dislikes of Users of the Properties. This information does not include any personally identifiable information. 

Please note that other information may be collected by third party analytics software we employ. Please read their privacy policies [here](http://getclicky.com/terms "Clicky Privacy Policy") and [here](http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy/ "Google Privacy Policy"). 

##  5\. Use of Personal Information 

**We will not sell or distribute your email address or any other personal information to any third parties.**

We may use the email address that you provided when you registered to contact you from time to time. This may be for security reasons (e.g. to reset your password), to ask your opinion about the Properties, or it may be to inform you of previous or future modifications to the Properties. It will not be to promote a third party's product. 

##  6\. Cookies 

We use cookies to identify you as a valid user and to help personalize your experience in conjunction with your profile. We are the only party that has access to these cookies. 

In addition, third party advertisers and services employed by the Properties may set cookies on your computer. While we make a concerted effort to screen third party advertisements and services, we can not control and can not be held responsible for any cookies set by those services. 

##  7\. Links 

We may display links to third party sites. However, we can not control and can not be held responsible for any other sites, their privacy policies or how they treat information about their users. You should read all website Terms of Use and Privacy Policies to determine how they are treating your personal information. 

##  8\. Advertising 

We may use third-party advertising companies to target and serve ads when you visit our Properties. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements of interest to you. These companies may employ cookies and other technologies to measure advertising effectiveness. 

Blendist does not guarantee the safety or accuracy of any third party site, advertisement, or product. Advertisers also have their own privacy policies and terms of service that must be carefully reviewed. 

**We will not serve advertisements from less than reputable third-party advertising companies. We have, and will continue to reject any advertisement opportunities that do not conform with this Policy.**

##  9\. Security 

**We protect your information with the latest standards in security and encryption.** We employ strong, one-way encryption methods to store passwords, and require secure certificates and passwords to access our database and server terminals. 

You should never disclose your account password to anyone. We use strong security measures to help keep your personal information safe, but we cannot guarantee that these measures will stop any users try to get around the privacy or security settings on the Properties through unforeseen and/or illegal activity, however small of a chance that may be. Consequently, you acknowledge that there are circumstances in which your personal information may be accessed by unauthorized persons. 

## 10\. General

The section titles in this Policy and the "Quick Overview" section above this Policy are for convenience only and have no legal or contractual effect.
